{
    "subject": "resource/Black_Prairie",
    "predicate": "ontology/hometown",
    "object": "resource/United_States",
    "human_readable": "Black Prairie's hometown is United States.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9227418899536133,
            "question": "Where is Black Prairie's hometown?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9097262024879456,
            "question": "Is Black Prairie from the United States?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4816264808177948,
            "question": "What is the population of Black Prairie?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.45079413056373596,
            "question": "What country is Black Prairie from?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.41534414887428284,
            "question": "Are there any famous people from Black Prairie?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3190745711326599,
            "question": "Where else might someone find information about Black Prairie?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2543310523033142,
            "question": "Does Black Prairie have any landmarks or historical sites?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.24915972352027893,
            "question": "What are some interesting facts about Black Prairie?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.22108638286590576,
            "question": "Can you tell me more about Black Prairie?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.1680479496717453,
            "question": "What is the climate like in Black Prairie?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Black Prairie's hometown is United States.",
            "html": "dbpedia_8844_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you tell me more about Black Prairie?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8844_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some interesting facts about Black Prairie?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8844_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Does Black Prairie have any landmarks or historical sites?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8844_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8844_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8844_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8844_20.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8844_25.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8844_53.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8844_56.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8844_65.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8844_66.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8844_73.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8844_78.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n``` \n\n\n\n\nThe provided text focuses on the history and experiences of Black people within prairie ecosystems, particularly in Canada. It does not mention a \"Black Prairie\" entity with a specific hometown.  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "Here is the JSON response:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nThis is because the context information provided indicates that the Black Prairie project and its related history are located in Alberta, Saskatchewan, and Manitoba (in Canada), not the United States."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\"output\": \"no\"}\n```\n\nExplanation: The provided documents do not contain any information related to the hometown of Black Prairie, nor do they mention Black Prairie having a specific hometown. The texts are about prairies in Illinois and Canada, as well as their historical significance regarding African-American/Black history, but there is no reference to \"Black Prairie\" or its location."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"no\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 0,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Most Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "mistral": {
            "reason": "Black Prairie refers to a historical context of Black communities living on the prairies in North America, specifically in Canada and the Midwestern United States. It does not refer to a specific hometown.",
            "category": 2
        },
        "gemma2": {
            "reason": "The text discusses Black Prairie history in Canada.",
            "category": 2
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "Black Prairie is primarily associated with Canada, not the United States.",
            "category": 2
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "reason": "The context information discusses Black prairie history primarily in the Canadian provinces of Alberta, Saskatchewan, and Manitoba, not in the United States.",
            "category": 2
        }
    }
}